<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hello Friend</title>
    
    
    
    <link>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://katekang0815.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Project Spark</title>
      <link>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/projectspark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/projectspark/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;http://katekang0815.github.io/img/spark/main.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          A central hub to view, collaborate, and comment on all cohort&amp;rsquo;s projects from the 19-week Hack Reactor Software Engineering Immersive program. Students of the May cohort and all future cohorts that could benefit from having a website dedicated to displaying sample projects, as well as all Hack Reactor staff and alumni.
Tech stack # Django REST framework, React, Python, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Docker, SimpleJWT auth
API design # For API endpoints for projects in-depth, look at API design
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Car Car</title>
      <link>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/carcar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/carcar/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;http://katekang0815.github.io/img/car/main.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          A CRUD app that allows Car dealers to manage inventory, technicians to track record of services and customers to create a service request. Enhanced backend Restful API endpoints to optimize data delivery and React hooks to manage stateful components.
Tech stack # Django REST framework, Python, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Docker, React, RESTful API&amp;rsquo;s
GHI Design # The three services intersect at a point represented by an Automobile. Each microservice interprets and focuses on it a different way.
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Go</title>
      <link>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/conferencego/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katekang0815.github.io/post/conferencego/</guid>
      <description>
        
          &lt;img src=&#34;http://katekang0815.github.io/img/conference/main.png&#34;/&gt;
          
        
        
        
          A conference &amp;amp; presentation aggregator web app for attendees and presenters. Developed full-stack, single-page web app with Restful API. Combined custom and third party API calls.Implemented poller/ rabbitMQ for communication between microservices.
Tech stack # Django REST framework, React, Python, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Docker, RabbitMQ, RabbitMQ, RESTful API&amp;rsquo;s
External API Integrations # Pexels API to get the URL of a picture of the city when create a new location instance
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>http://katekang0815.github.io/archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://katekang0815.github.io/archive/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
          
          
        
        
        
          
          
        
        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>